//Questions array
            let questions = [
            {
                 number:1,
                 question: "15−3×2+4=",
                 answer : "13",
                 options : [
                                  "16",
                                  "13",
                                  "10",
                                  "8"
                                ]
            
            },
            {
                 number:2,
                 question: "24÷3+6×2=",
                 answer : "20",
                 options : [
                                  "3",
                                  "4",
                                  "5",
                                  "20"  
                                  ]
            
            },
           {
                 number:3,
                 question: "9×(4+2)÷3",
                 answer : "18",
                 options : [ 
                                  "30",
                                  "18",
                                  "15",
                                  "12"
                                  ]
            
            },
            {
                 number:4,
                 question: "10−(3×2)+5=",
                 answer : "9",
                 options : [
                                  "20",
                                  "24",
                                  "30",
                                  "9"
                                  ]
            }, 
            {
                 number:5,
                 question: "16÷(4−1)×2=",
                 answer : "10.7",
                 options : [ 
                                  "8",
                                  "9",
                                  "10.7",
                                  "12"
                               ]
            },
            {
                 number:6,
                 question: "20−3÷3+4=",
                 answer : "23",
                 options : [
                                  "2",
                                  "23",
                                  "4",
                                  "5"
                               ]
            },
            {
                 number:7,
                 question: "5×(2+3)−4=",
                 answer : "21",
                 options : [
                                  "21",
                                  "15",
                                  "9",
                                  "8"
                               ]
            },
             {
                 number:8,
                 question: "36÷(6×2)+3=",
                 answer : "6",
                 options : [
                                 "10",
                                 "8",
                                 "6",
                                 "5"
                               ]
            },
            {
                 number:9,
                 question: "12×2−6÷3=",
                 answer : "22",
                 options : [
                                 "22",
                                 "15",
                                 "18",
                                 "20"
                               ]
            },
            {
               number:10,
               question: "18−6÷2+5=",
               answer : "20",
               options : [
                               "10",
                               "20",
                               "8",
                               "6"
                             ]
          },
          {
               number:11,
               question: " 7×(4−2)+3=",
               answer : "17",
               options : [
                               "17",
                               "2",
                               "3",
                               "4"
                             ]
          },
          {
               number:12,
               question: "48÷(4×3)−2=",
               answer : "2",
               options : [
                               "14",
                               "16",
                               "18",
                               "2"
                             ]
          },
          {
               number:13,
               question: "15−3×2+4=",
               answer : "13",
               options : [
                               "8",
                               "13",
                               "12",
                               "18"
                             ]
          },
          {
               number:14,
               question: " 30÷5×3−2=",
               answer : "16",
               options : [
                               "16",
                               "35",
                               "29",
                               "27"
                             ]
          },
          {
               number:15,
               question: "8×(3+2)−7=",
               answer : "33",
               options : [
                               "33",
                               "16",
                               "18",
                               "20"
                             ]
          }
          ,
          {
               number:16,
               question: "45÷(5×2)+3=",
               answer : "7.5",
               options : [
                               "5",
                               "6",
                               "7.5",
                               "8"
                             ]
          }
          ,
          {
               number:17,
               question: " 20−4÷2×3=",
               answer : "14",
               options : [
                               "17",
                               "13",
                               "18",
                               "14"
                             ]
          }
          ,
          {
               number:18,
               question: "12÷3+6×2=",
               answer : "16",
               options : [
                               "7",
                               "16",
                               "22",
                               "20"
                             ]
          }
          ,
          {
               number:19,
               question: "9×(5−3)+4=",
               answer : "22",
               options : [
                               "12",
                               "14",
                               "18",
                               "22"
                             ]
          }
          ,
          {
               number:20,
               question: "64÷(8×2)−3=",
               answer : "1",
               options : [
                               "1",
                               "2",
                               "3",
                               "4"
                             ]
          }
             ];